	⁃	1. No, <!DOCTYPE html>
	⁃	2. <html lang=“en”>
	⁃	Needs to be above head 
	⁃	4. Missing meta charset
	⁃	5. Missing meta name
	⁃	7. Missing closing tag for head
	⁃	8. No h1 closing tag
	⁃	10. No paragraph opening tag
	⁃	12 - 23. Mismatched tags for bullet list
	⁃	For an ordered list should be an ol closing tag
	⁃	25. No closing tag for paragraph
	⁃	27. No alt attributes for image
	⁃	29. Wrong closing tag, no target
	⁃	38. No closing / for td
	⁃	44. No closing tag for table
	⁃	46. It isn’t source it is src for an image
	⁃	48. Center is obsolete in modern html so you have to use CSS
	⁃	50. Wrong way to color text
	⁃	54. Unclosed comment
	⁃	56. Unclosed link without closing tag, also technically no link
	⁃	58. Em end tag should be before the p end tag
	⁃	60-63. For description lists you have to use dt for the title of the item, and dd for the text
